<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Prose for App.net]]></title>
  <link href="http://prose-app.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://prose-app.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-03T23:46:39+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://prose-app.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Shawn Throop]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Now?]]></title>
    <link href="http://prose-app.github.io/blog/2014/08/21/why-now/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-21T18:49:15+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://prose-app.github.io/blog/2014/08/21/why-now</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since the App.net <a href="http://blog.app.net/2014/05/06/app-net-state-of-the-union/">State of the Union announcement</a> there have been many discussions about App.net, its success, and its ability to continue running. Regardless of those discussions and the fact that App.net remains a functioning service, I believe it is no longer an economically viable platform to build apps on.</p>

<p>So why would I continue to create a client application for a service that might disappear before it&rsquo;s approved by Apple?</p>

<p>There are two important facts that allowed Prose to be finished: I have a stable &ldquo;day job&rdquo; and Prose is my first app. I started learning Objective-C at around this time last year and not until I was actually writing Prose did I really learn it<sup id="fnref:1"><a href="#fn:1" rel="footnote">1</a></sup>. Prose is a passion project and regardless of sales, I have already profited from it: I know Objective-C, I know how to make an iOS app, and I am confident that my current knowledge will help me adapt as a developer (switching to Swift, for example).</p>

<h3>What Comes Next</h3>

<p>Just because I have shipped an app doesn&rsquo;t mean I&rsquo;m done with it. I wanted to make an iOS app and supporting it, fixing bugs, and shipping updates are all a part of that.</p>

<p>I wish I could promise to actively develop Prose forever but I don&rsquo;t know App.net’s future and I won&rsquo;t lie to customers. I’ll be using App.net until the API ceases to respond and I want to use Prose until that time comes.</p>

<p>What I can confidently say is that, as of now, <strong>I will continue to actively develop Prose</strong>. I have more features planned and I will fix bugs for as long as I can. If a time comes where I need to re-evaluate that statement I will let you know.</p>

<p>Follow <a href="http://app.net/prose">@prose</a> or <a href="http://app.net/c/w2m8">subscribe to the Broadcast channel</a> to get notified of updates. For a more personal touch follow me, <a href="http://app.net/shawnthroop">@shawnthroop</a>.</p>
<div class="footnotes">
<hr/>
<ol>
<li id="fn:1">
<p>Don&rsquo;t let this scare you. As my knowledge of Objective-C grew I rewrote the main timeline 14 times and the whole app 3 times before it was released.<a href="#fnref:1" rev="footnote">&#8617;</a></p></li>
</ol>
</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Prose]]></title>
    <link href="http://prose-app.github.io/blog/2014/08/21/announcing-prose/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-21T06:34:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://prose-app.github.io/blog/2014/08/21/announcing-prose</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Prose is a new client for App.net. It&rsquo;s uses three panes and a simple swipe navigation to provide an uncluttered and useful App.net experience.</p>

<h2>Features</h2>

<p>Prose supports the features of any basic App.net client as well as some others:</p>

<ul>
<li><p><strong>Multiple accounts</strong> - Sign into more than one account with ease, App.net Passport and 1Password are supported. Quickly switch between accounts by tapping on the navigation bar from any pane.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Push notifications</strong> - Keep up to date and choose which types of notifications you receive on a per-account basis.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Advanced composing</strong> - Post messages with inline markdown links and attach photos in the camera roll or taken in the app. Prose smartly cleans up images from your App.net storage if you decide not to post them.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Robust sharing</strong> - Save links for later with Instapaper, Pocket, Pinboard, Readability, and Safari&rsquo;s Reading List. Annotating Pinboard links is supported natively.</p></li>
<li><p><strong>Stream marker</strong> - Prose will automatically update your reading position so you can use App.net from multiple platforms and apps without loosing your place.</p></li>
</ul>


<p>Prose was designed to be simple, uncluttered, and most of all useful. Get it <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/prose-for-app.net/id900900989?ls=1&amp;mt=8">on the App Store</a> today.</p>

<p>Follow <a href="http://app.net/prose">@prose</a> to keep up to date and <a href="http://app.net/c/w2m8">subscribe to the broadcast channel</a> to be notified when updates are available.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
